Charles Scribner's Sons Art Reference Department
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Portrait Files, 1839-1962, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-5, 7, OV 12; 4.4 linear feet)
  - Mary I of England; Mary of Orange, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Mary, Queen of Scots, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - A.E.W. Mason; Massena, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Jules Massenet; Cotton Mather; Cardinal Mazarin, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - William Gibbs McAdoo, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Isaac McKeever; Philip Ainsworth Means; Cosimo de Medici; Etienne Henri Méhul; Melanethon; Mlle. Melba, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Felix Mendelssohn, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - George Meredith, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Lucien Metivet; Jacob Meyerbeer, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Michelangelo; Sir John Millais, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - William Miller; Jean-François Millet, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Richard Monckton Milnes; John Milton, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - King Mindon; The Kinwun Mingye, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Donald G. Mitchell, 1902, undated, (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 36-39)
  - S. Weir Mitchell, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - George A. Moffitt, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Molière; Theodor Mommsen, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Edward Montagu; Marquis de Montcalm; Baron de Montesquieu; Albert Moore; Henry More; Sir Henry Morgan; Lewis Henry Morgan, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - William Morris, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Samuel F. B. Morse, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Ignaz Moscheles, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - William Sidney Mount, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Hermann Mueller; Jules Muenier, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Benito Mussolini; Modest Mussorgski, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Abdel Nader, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Napoleon Bonaparte, 1913, undated, (11 folders) (Box 3, Folder 51-61)
  - Napoleon III, 1839, undated, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 62-63)
  - Nefritete; Lord Nelson; Nero, undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Cardinal John Henry Newman, undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Sir Isaac Newton; Marshal Ney; Nicholas, Emperor of Russia; Meredith Nicholson; Nostradamus, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Alfred Noyes, undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Oberhardl, undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Tomas O'Crohan, undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Odysseus, undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Jacques Offenbach; Mrs. M. O. W. Oliphant; W. Q. Orchardson; Abraham Ortelius; Sean O'Sullivan, 1880, undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Johann Palestrina; Lord Palmerston; Panku; Mary Panton, undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Sir Gilbert Parker, undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Francis Parkman, undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Robert E. Peary and Mrs. Peary, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Sir Robert Peel, undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Captain Ernest Peixotto, undated, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 77-78)
  - Edward Penfield, undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - William Penn; Joseph Pennell; Stanley Pennell; Hugh, Earl Percy; Peter the Great of Russia; Peter the Hermit; Petrarch; King Philip; Philp of Burgundy; Philip II of Spain; Philip IV of Spain, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Franklin Pierce, undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - William Pitt the Elder; William Pitt the Younger; James K. Polk; Marco Polo, undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Alexander Pope, undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Pope Gregory I; Pope Gregory VII; Pope Leo X; Pope Paul III; Pope Pio Nono; Pope Pius VII, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Countess Potocka; Cora Urquhart Potter; J. Poynter, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - William Hickling Prescott; May Wilson Preston; Pierre Joseph Proudhon; William Prynne; Alexander Pushkin, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Howard Pyle, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - John Pym; Pythagoras, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Quarles; A. T. Quiller-Couch, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - François Rabelais; Jean Racine; Sir Walter Raleigh, 1899, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - John Randolph; General John A. Rawlins, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Marjorie Kinnon Rawlins, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Madame Recamier; Regulus, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Frederic Remington, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Ernst Renan, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Paul Revere; Sir Joshua Reynolds, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Louis Rhead, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Richard I; Richard III; Samuel Richardson, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Cardinal Richelieu; James Whitcomb Riley; George Ripley; Lady Ripon, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Frederick Sleigh Roberts; James Robertson; Robespierre, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Auguste Rodin, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - John Rogers; Samuel Rogers; Roland; M. Georges Roland; King of Romania; W. S. Rosecranz, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Mrs. Rossetti and Miss Christina Rossetti; Otto Roth, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Jean Jacques Rousseau; Theodore Rousseau; Peter Paul Rubens; Anton Rubinstein; Prince Rupert, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - John Ruskin, 1897, undated, (5 folders) (Box 4, Folder 20-24)
  - Charles Russell; Martin Rutter; Admiral de Ruyter, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Richard Sackville; Russell Sage; Camille Saint-Saëns; Antonio Salieri; Lord and Lady Salisbury, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - George Sand, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Dr. R. Sanderson, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - John Singer Sargent, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Savanarola, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Alessandro Scarlatti; Sir George Scharf; Johann Hermann Schein; Schiller; F.E.D. Schleiermacher, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Franz Schubert, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Heinrich Schütz; Peter Schuyler, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Sir Walter Scott, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Segatini; Ludwig Senfl; Michael Servetus; Joseph Severn, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Samuel Sewall; William H. Seward; Lady Jane Seymour; Ludovico Sforza; Robert Shackleton, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Shakespeare, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Commodore Thompson Shaw; Mary Wollstonecraft Shelley; Percy Bysshe Shelley, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - General Philip H. Sheridan; John Sherman; Stuart Sherman; William Tecumseh Sherman, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Sir Philip Sidney; Lydia Huntley Sigourney; Benjamin Sillimen, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - John Sloan, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Adam Smith, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - F. Hopkinson Smith, 1908, undated, (4 folders) (Box 4, Folder 43-46)
  - Henry Smith, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Joaquin Sorolla y Bastida, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - John Hanning Speke and James Grant; Edmund Spencer; George John Spencer; Herbert Spencer, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Laurence Stallings; Miles Standish; Arthur Penrhyn Stanley; Stanwyck?, 1928, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Richard Steele, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Beatrice Stevens; Frank R. Stockton; Marian Storm, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - William Wetmore Story, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Thomas Stothard; Harriet Beecher Stowe; Richard Strauss, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Igor Stravinsky; Charles Stuart, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Henry Stuart; Henry Benedict Stuart; James Stuart, undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Mary Stuart; Alexander McCormick Sturm; Thomas, Earl of Surry; Jonathan Swift; Algernon Charles Swinburne; J. A. Symonds; Count Szechenyi, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Tallyrand; Richard Tarlton; Carl Taussig, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Annie R. Taylor; Sir Henry Taylor; Jeremy Taylor; Tom Taylor; Zachary Taylor, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Piotr Ilyitch Tchaikovsky; William Tell, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Alfred Lord Tennyson, undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - William Makepeace Thackeray, 1903-1945, undated, (8 folders) (Box 4, Folder 62-69)
  - Theodorich; Theseus; Amédée Thierry; Adolphe Thiers; M. Thiers; Henry David Thoreau; Matthew Thornton, undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Albert Thorwaldsen, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - George Ticknor; Tippoo Sultaun, undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Leo Tolstoy, 1928, undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Trajan; E. J. Trelawney, 1895, undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Paul Troubetzkoy, undated (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Commodore Truxtun, undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Ivan Turgenev, undated, (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 77-79)
  - Turgot; John Tyler, undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Niccolo da Uzzano; Marguerite de Valois, undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Martin Van Buren; Van der Werff; Henry Van Dyke; Sir Henry Vane, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Elihu Vedder, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Verderber; Giuseppe Verdi; Jules Verne; Paul Veronese, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Victoria, Crown Princess of Germany, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
  - Daniel Vièrge, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Barbara Villiers; George Villiers, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - François Villon, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Alexander Volta; Voltaire; Harry Von Arnim, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hans von Bülow; Prof. von Helmholtz; General Von Hindenburg, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Alexander von Humboldt, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Wilhelm von Humboldt; Marie von Rumänien, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - M. Waddington, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Richard Wagner; Martin Waldseemuller; Robert Walker; Sir William Walker, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sir William Waller; Robert Walpole; Izaak Walton; Mrs. Humphrey Ward, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Olin Levi Warner, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Lord De La Warr; Samuel Warren, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - George Washington, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 17-18)
  - William Watson; James Watt, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - G. F. Watts, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Isaac Watts; Frederick Judd Waugh; Daniel Webster, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Thurlow Weed; Duke of Wellington; H. G. Wells; King Wenceslas, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Lord Sackville West; Christina Weston; Governor General Weyler; Earl of Wharncliffe, 1940, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Edith Wharton, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Walt Whitman; Caspar Whitney; Gertrude Vanderbilt Whitney, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - John Greenleaf Whittier; Wiclif; William Wilberforce, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Irving R. Wiles, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Queen Wilhelmina; Rev. William Willett; William the Conqueror; William the Silent; William II of Nassau, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Emperor William I of Prussia, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Miss Willis; Edmund Wilson; John Winthrop, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 7) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Friedrich August Wolf; James Wolfe, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Thomas Wolff, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - William Wordsworth, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Sir Henry Wotton; W. Wycherley, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - N. C. Wyeth, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Ahmedi Xani, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Jack B. Yeats; William B. Yeats, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - F. C. Yohn; Thomas Young; Count of Zinzendorf; Emile Zola, 1903, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Anders Zorn; Ulrich Zwingle, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Oversized Drawing of Unidentified Man by Francisca Bolles, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F1) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Photograph of Charcoal Drawing of "George" by John Singer Sargent, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F1) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Photograph of a Bust of John Adams, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F4) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Charcoal Drawing of H. Baass by Francisca Bolles, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F22) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Ink and Charcoal Drawing of Thomas Bertram by Lydia Hess, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F38) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Charcoal Drawing of Boyd by K. S. Woerner, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F48) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Charcoal Drawing of Boyd by an Unidentified Artist, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F48) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Engraving of William Cullen Bryant, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F51) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Charcoal Drawing of V. F. Calverton by Francisca Bolles, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F63) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Color Pencil Drawing of the Duchess of Cambridge by George T. Tobin, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F63) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Etchings of Copeland by D. C. Sturges, undated, (Scanned with Box 1, F85) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Red Chalk Drawing of Suydam Cutting, 1935, (Scanned with Box 2, F4) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Pencil Drawing of Dr. Leopold Damrosch, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F5) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Block Print of Richard Harding Davis, 1912, (Scanned with Box 2, F11) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Photograph of a Painting of Admiral David G. Farragut, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F31) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Charcoal and Ink Drawings of F. Scott Fitzgerald by Francisca Bolles, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F34) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Charcoal Drawing of Peter Fleming by Francisca Bolles, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F37) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Photograph of John Galsworthy by Arnold Genthe, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F43-47) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Three Oversized Photographs of John Galsworthy by Unidentified Photographers, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F43-47) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Ink Drawing of John Galsworthy, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F43-47) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Block Print of John Galsworthy, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F43-47) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Conte Crayon Drawing of Charles George "Chinese" Gordon by George T. Tobin, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F55) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Charcoal Drawing of Nancy Hall by Francisca Bolles, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F61) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Photograph of Lithograph of Washington Irving, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F82) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Charcoal Drawing of Jean-François Millet by Carroll Beckwith, undated, (Scanned with Box 3, F33) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Ink Drawing of Meredith Nicholson by McKee, undated, (Scanned with Box 3, F66) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Charcoal Drawing of Joseph Pennell by Elizabeth Horton, undated, (Scanned with Box 3, F80) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized photograph of charcoal drawing of Stanley Pennell by Elizabeth Horton, undated, (Scanned with Box 3, F80) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Ink Drawings of Marjorie Kinnon Rawlins, undated, (Scanned with Box 4, F7) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Color Pencil Drawings of Lord and Lady Salisbury by George T. Tobin, undated, (Scanned with Box 4, F26) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Copy Photograph of General Philip H. Sheridan and Generals George A. Custer, Thomas C. Devin, James W. Forsyth, and Wesley Merritt, undated, (Scanned with Box 4, F39) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Block Prints of Stuart Sherman, undated, (Scanned with Box 4, F39) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Red Chalk Drawing of Laurence Stallings by McNerney, 1928, (Scanned with Box 4, F50) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Charcoal Drawing of Henry Van Dyke by Walter Appleton Clark, undated, (Scanned with Box 4, F82) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Pencil Drawing of Thomas Verderber, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F2) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Pencil Drawing of Christina Weston by Waldo Peirce, 1940, (Scanned with Box 5, F23) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Ink Drawing of Edmund Wilson, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F30) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Oversized Charcoal Drawing of John Galsworthy by Stevenson, undated, (Scanned with Box 2, F43-47) (Box OV 12)
- Illustrator Files, 1878-1921, undated, Series 2:; (Box 5-6, 8, OV 9-OV12; 1.5 linear feet)
  These files contain both original and reproductions of art work that is not portraiture. The file for unidentified artists includes ink drawings of Civil War soldiers, a tempera painting for the cover of Boot Straps: Autobiography of Tom M. Girdler, and an oil painting for A Child's Garden of Verse. There is original art work by Otto Bacher, Lowell LeRoy Balcom, Wladyslaw Theodore Benda, Carl Michel Boog, Paul Bransom, S. R. Burleigh, George Carlson, Carl Cobbledick, A. R. Dugmore, G. W. Edwards, Walter H. Everett, John Fulleylove, William St. John Harper, O. Herford, Arthur E. Jameson, J. E. Kelly, Charles R. Knight, M. Jean McLean, E. J. Meeker, E. C. Peixotto, Victor S. Perard, J. Campbell Phillips, Shipley, Sarah S. Stilwell, Jack Van Ryder, George Varian, H. D. Williams, and N. C. Wyeth.
  - Unidentified Artists, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Edwin Austin Abbey, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - S. M. Arthurs, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Otto Bacher, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Lowell LeRoy Balcom, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Wladyslaw Theodore Benda, undated, (Oversized items housed in OV 12) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Reginald Birch, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Carl Michel Boog, 1921, (Oversized items housed in OV 9) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Paul Bransom, 1920, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - S. R. Burleigh, 1900, undated, (5 folders) (Box 5, Folder 49-53)
  - George Carlson, undated, (Oversized items housed in OV 9) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Carlton T. Chapman, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - William Appleton Clark, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Carl Cobbledick, undated, (Oversized items housed in OV 10) (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - George Cruikshank, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - A. R. Dugmore, 1900, (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 59-61)
  - G. W. Edwards, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Walter H. Everett, 1916, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Florian, undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - A. B. Frost, undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - John Fulleylove, undated, (6 folders) (Box 5, Folder 66-71)
  - Charles Dana Gibson, undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Gordon Grant, 1903, (Oversized items housed in OV 10) (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Vaughn Gray, undated, (Oversized items housed in OV 10) (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Haberstock, undated, (Oversized items housed in OV 10) (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - William St. John Harper, 1896, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - O. Herford, undated (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Will James, undated (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Arthur E. Jameson, undated, (2 folders; Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 79-80)
  - John, undated, (Oversized items housed in OV 10) (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - J. E. Kelly, 1878 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Charles R. Knight, 1900-1901, (Oversized items housed in OV 11) (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - M. Jean McLean, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - E. J. Meeker, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - E. C. Peixotto, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Victor S. Perard, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - J. Campbell Phillips, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Howard Pyle, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 89-90)
  - Hy Reuterdahl, undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Shipley, undated (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Jessie Willcox Smith, undated (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Sarah S. Stilwell, undated, (8 folders) (Box 5, Folder 94-101)
  - Thorpe, 1906, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Jack Van Ryder, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - George Varian, 1918, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - I. W., undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - H. D. Williams, undated, (3 folders; Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 6, Folder 2-4)
  - N. C. Wyeth, 1910, undated, (3 folders; Oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 6, Folder 5-7)
  - F. C. Yohn, undated, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
  - Two Oversized Ink Drawings of Civil War Soldiers by an Unidentified Artist, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F40) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Oversized Tempera Painting for the Cover of Boot Straps: Autobiography of Tom M. Girdler by an Unidentified Artist, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F40) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Oversized Oil Painting for A Child's Garden of Verse by an Unidentified Artist, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F40) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Four Oversized Photographs of Murals by Edwin Austin Abbey, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F41) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Ink and Watercolor Illustrations by Paul Bransom, 1920, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F48) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Oversized Ink Drawing by G. W. Edwards for the Cover of Hans Brinker or the Silver Skates by Mary Mapes Dodge, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F62) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Oversized Oil Painting "Spanning the Continent by Rail" by Walter H. Everett, 1916, (Scanned with Box 5, F63) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Ink Drawings of the Aftermath of the Johnstown Flood and of the City Hall in Richmond by William St. John Harper, 1896, (Scanned with Box 5, F76) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Ink Drawings of Civil War Scenes by Arthur E. Jameson, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F79-80) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Three Oversized Watercolor Paintings by M. Jean McLean, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F84) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Ink Drawings of the Peace Palace in The Hague and of Wall Street in the Seventeenth Century by E. J. Meeker, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F85) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Oversized Ink Drawing of a Building in San Antonio by E. C. Peixotto, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F86) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Ink Drawings of Civil War Scenes by Victor S. Perard, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F87) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Four Oversized Ink Drawings of Civil War Scenes by J. Campbell Phillips, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F88) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Oversized Etching of Old Trinity Church by Thorpe, 1906, (Scanned with Box 5, F102) (Box 8 (sol))
  - An Oversized Sheet of Pencil Drawings of Mexican Images by Jack Van Ryder, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F103) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Three Oversized Ink and Watercolor Drawings for Treasure Island by George Varian, 1918, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F104) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Oversized Ink Drawing by I. W. for The Hero in America by Dixon Wecter, undated, (Scanned with Box 6, F1) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Five Oversized Ink Drawings for the Child-Lore Dramatic Reader by H. D. Williams, undated, (Scanned with Box 6, F2-4) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Oversized Ink Drawing by N. C. Wyeth for Portrait of a Philosopher by Dorothy Canfield, 1910, (Scanned with Box 6, F5-7) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Three Oversized Watercolor Drawings by Carl Michel Boog for the "How It Came About Stories," 1921, (Scanned with Box 5, F47) (Box OV 9)
  - Oversized Ink Drawing by George Carlson for Stately Timbers by Rupert Hughes, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F54) (Box OV 9)
  - Oversized Ink Drawing by Carl Cobbledick for the Cover of White Sails Crowding, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F57) (Box OV 10)
  - Oversized Ink and Gouache Painting of a Civil War Scene by Gordon Grant, 1903, (Scanned with Box 5, F73) (Box OV 10)
  - Two Oversized Ink Drawings of Maps of Custer's Last Stand by Vaughn Gray, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F74) (Box OV 10)
  - Oversized Ink Drawing by Haberstock for The Last Puritan by George Santayana, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F75) (Box OV 10)
  - Oversized Watercolor Drawing by John for Richard Pryne by Cyril Harris, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F81) (Box OV 10)
  - Five Oversized Tempera Paintings by Charles R. Knight for The World of the Great Forest, 1900-1901, (Scanned with Box 5, F83) (Box OV 11)
  - Three Oversized Charcoal Drawings by Wladyslaw Theodore Benda, undated, (Scanned with Box 5, F45) (Box OV 12)